mitfcu2.org 2019-04-18

# FACTS

Privacy Policy
FACTS                   WHAT DOES MIT FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR
                        PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                    Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
                        gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires
                        us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please
                        read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?                   The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or
                        service you have with us. This information can include:
                                  • Social Security Number			                    • Transaction history
                                  • Account balances			                          • Credit history
                                  • Payment history			                           • Account transactions
                        When you are no longer a member, we continue to share your information as described
                        in this notice.
How?                    All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their
                        everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can
                        share their members’ personal information; the reasons MIT Federal Credit Union
                        chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
    Reasons we can share your personal                  Does MIT Federal Credit              Can you limit this
                  information.                                Union share?                        sharing?
For our everyday business purposes -
such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                    Yes                              No
your account(s), respond to court orders, and
legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes -
to offer our products and services to you                           Yes                              No
For joint marketing with other financial
                                                                    Yes                              No
companies
For our affiliates’ everyday business
purposes - information about your                                   No                         We don’t share
transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business
purposes - information about your                                   No                         We don’t share
creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                  No                         We don’t share
Questions?               Call 617-253-2845 or go to www.mitfcu.org
            700 Technology Square, Building NE48 Cambridge, MA 02139-3586 T: 617-253-2845 F: 617-258-5709

Privacy Policy
 Page 2
 What We Do
How does MIT Federal        To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
Credit Union protect        security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include
my personal                 computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
information?                We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect
                            this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom
                            access is appropriate.
How does MIT Federal We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Credit Union collect                  • Open an account		                  • Provide account information
my personal                           • Apply for a loan			                • Give us your contact information
information?                          • Apply for financing
                            We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                            affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all       Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing?                              • sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes - information about
                                        your creditworthiness
                                      • affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                      • sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                            State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit
                            sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
 Definitions
 Affiliates                 Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial
                            and non-financial companies.
                            • MIT Federal Credit Union does not share with our affiliates.
 Nonaffiliates              Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial
                            and non-financial companies.
                            • MIT Federal Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
 Joint Marketing            A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together
                            market financial products or services to you.
                            • Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies, investment companies, and
                            direct marketing companies.
 Other Important Information
For Alaska, Illinois, Maryland and North Dakota Members. We will not share personal information
with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization.
For California Members. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates either for them to
market to you or for joint marketing - without your authorization. We will also limit our sharing of personal
information about you with our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us.
For Massachusetts, Mississippi and New Jersey Members. We will not share personal information from
deposit or share relationships with nonaffiliates either for them to market to you or for joint marketing -
without your authorization.
For Vermont Members. We will not share personal information with nonaffiliates for them to market to
you without your authorization and we will not share personal information with affiliates or for joint
marketing about your creditworthiness without your authorization.
            700 Technology Square, Building NE48 Cambridge, MA 02139-3586 T: 617-253-2845 F: 617-258-5709
                                                                                                                 Rev. 6/2013
